<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DPTechLab</title><link>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/</link><description>Recent content on DPTechLab</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© DPTechLab</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 19:01:48 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Git Config</title><link>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/posts/post/gitconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 19:01:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/posts/post/gitconfig/</guid><description>Git configuration command Git config allows you to set various configuration options for git.
Setting global username and email. git config --global user.name ardbp git config --global user.email panchaldaxesh@gmailc.om Add new remote url to git git remote add origin https://github.com/ardbp/grpctemplate.git Updating remote url to git git remote set-url origin https://github.com/ardbp/grpctemplate.git or git remote set-url origin git@github.com:ardbp/grpctemplate.git Display remote url git remote -v Using ssh over https using git config git config --global url.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Github Pages</title><link>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/posts/post/githubpages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 03:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/posts/post/githubpages/</guid><description>How to Deploy OpenAPI specs using Github Pages Enable github Pages First step is to enable gh-pages for your repository Next Select Pages from Settings menu of your repository Select visibility Public/Private based on who you wants to share your API specs Next Select Deploy from branch option in source Next select branch and directory where your API specs is available. Optionally you can select Theme and Custom domain. When you will specify custom domain gh-pages will be deploy using custom domain instead of ardbp.</description></item><item><title>Template Repository</title><link>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/posts/post/templaterepo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 15:43:48 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ardbp.github.io/dpcontent/posts/post/templaterepo/</guid><description>Github Template repository Github template repository will allow to create new repository with the same directory structure and files as it is available in github template repository.
This could be very useful for createing service-template and few other things.
How to convert an existing repository to Template repository. Visit GitHub.com, navigate to the main page of your repository. Under your repository name, click Settings. From the General section, Select template repository How to Create repository from Template repository Option 1.</description></item></channel></rss>